fatsickandnearlydead.com 2016-10-19

# About the Film | Fat Sick & Nearly Dead

## Fat, Sick & Nearly Dead Privacy Policy

We understand that your privacy is important and we respect your privacy choices. In addition, we want to ensure that you know exactly how your information may be used. This Privacy Policy reflects our commitment to those principles and explains:

  * Information we collect
  * How we use your information
  * How we protect your information
  * Choices you have regarding your personal information
  * How to contact us

This Privacy Policy applies to web sites owned and operated by Reboot USA, LLC.

 **Information We Collect**

 _Personal Information_

Should you provide it, we may collect the following types of information from you ("Personal Information"), which may include information that can be used to identify you:

  * Name
  * Age
  * Email Address
  * Mailing Address
  * Telephone Number(s)
  * Credit Card Information
  * Social Networking Handle or Username
  * Photo or Video

In certain cases, we may request that you provide some of the information identified above in order to obtain specific products or services. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you may still use our web site but you may be unable to access certain features or services. When you register to receive any products or services from FSND or provide information to FSND in any other manner, you agree to provide only true, accurate, current and complete information.

_Non-Personal Information_

We may automatically receive and log certain types of information that cannot be used to identify you ("Non-Personal Information") when you visit or interact with the Fat, Sick & Nearly Dead ("FSND") web site, services, Apps or other products, including:

  * Browser Information
  * Operating System Information
  * Mobile Device Information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)
  * IP Address
  * Internet Service Provider
  * Content Viewed
  * Geographic Location
  * Connection Speed
  * Time of Visit
  * Referring Site, Application or Service
  * Registration Time

Non-Personal Information about your use of the FSND web site and your use of other web sites is collected through the use of Cookies and Web Beacons. "Cookies" are small data files that are stored on the hard drive of the computer you use to view a web site. Every computer that accesses the FSND web site is assigned a unique cookie by us. "Web Beacons" are graphic image files imbedded in a web page typically used to monitor activity on a web page and send back to its home server (which can belong to the host site, a network advertiser or some other third party) information from your browser, such as the IP address, the URL of the page on which the Web Beacon is located, the type browser that is accessing the site and the ID number of any Cookies on your computer previously placed by that server.

In addition, third parties under contract with FSND may use Cookies or Web Beacons to collect Non-Personal Information about your usage of the FSND web site. These third party advertising service providers may use this information, on our behalf, to help FSND deliver advertising on the FSND web site as well as on other sites on the Internet based on your browsing activity on our sites. FSND may further tailor the advertising on these third party sites based on additional Non-Personal Information to the extent known by FSND or these third parties.

 _Social Networking Sites_

If you choose to use any third party website or service that is integrated with FSND, such as Facebook, Google+ or Twitter ("Social Networking Sites"), we may receive Personal Information from such Social Networking Sites, including, but not limited to:

  * Name
  * Nickname or Username
  * Photo or Graphic Avatar
  * Unique Third Party Website Identifier (e.g., Facebook User ID)
  * Biographical or Demographic Information (e.g. professional title, gender, college attended, etc.)
  * Likes and Interests
  * Contacts / Friends / Associations
  * Any Information that Is Publicly Available on Third Party Websites

FSND offers the ability to use certain Social Networking Sites to facilitate your registration on the FSND web site. We may also use information about your profile and connections on Social Networking Sites to allow you to share or connect with your friends and contacts on FSND or to personalize your experience.

Your decision to use, or share with, a Social Networking Site when accessing or using the FSND web site is completely voluntary. FSND is not responsible for compliance with the policies or practices of any Social Networking Site. You should ensure that you are comfortable with the information such Social Networking Sites may make available to FSND by reviewing those Social Networking Sites' privacy policies and service terms, and by modifying your privacy settings and preferences on those web sites accordingly.

Any information we receive from Social Networking Sites will be governed by this Privacy Policy.

 _Analytics Services_

FSND uses third party analytics providers and products to obtain, compile and analyze information (that may include Personal Information) about how users are using and interacting with the FSND web site. FSND may provide information (including Personal Information) to these analytics providers for the purpose of obtaining statistics and other information about how users are using and interacting with the FSND web site. These analytics providers may use tracking techniques other than Cookies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect or compile this information. These techniques may be used directly on the FSND web site. FSND has no responsibility for the technologies, tools or practices of the third parties that provide analytics products and services to FSND. Please be aware that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these techniques, and that browser settings that block conventional Cookies may have no effect on such techniques.

Non-Personal Information Collected by Third Parties Not Acting on FSND's Behalf

We work with third parties to display advertising that reflects the interests and preferences of our users. Sponsors or advertisers on the FSND web site may use their own Cookies, Web Beacons or other online tracking technologies in the banner advertisements served on the FSND web site and in emails, special promotions, Daily Posts or Newsletters we send you. Their advertisements may be displayed on the FSND web site or on other sites that you visit after you visit the FSND web site. Some advertisers use companies other than FSND to serve their ads and to monitor users' responses to ads, and these companies ("Ad Servers") may also collect Non-Personal Information through the use of Cookies or Web Beacons on the FSND web site.

We do not control how third parties use Cookies or Web Beacons or how they manage the Non-Personal Information they gather through the use of these technologies on the FSND web site. However, we do require sponsors, advertisers and Ad Servers who collect Cookie or Web Beacon information through the FSND web site to agree that they will not collect any Personal Information from the FSND web site without your consent. They have promised us they will not link any Non-Personal Information collected by them on the FSND web site to Personal Information they or others collect in other ways or from other sites.

 **How We Use Your Information**

We may use information we collect about you to:

  * Administer your account
  * Provide you with access to particular services
  * Respond to your inquiries and send you communications
  * Obtain your feedback on our sites and our offerings
  * Statistically analyze user behavior and activity
  * Provide you with more relevant content and advertisements
  * Conduct research and measurement activities
  * Send you personalized emails or secure electronic messages pertaining to your interests, including news, announcements, reminders and opportunities

_Use of Personal Information_

We use the information we obtain from you to provide FSND products and services, fulfill your requests, improve our products and services, personalize and tailor your experience on our web site, operate our business, and understand how users are engaging with FSND. In addition, we may use information from you to facilitate the delivery of content or advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you, or to communicate with you about new or existing products and services or special offers.

FSND does not make your Personal Information available to third parties for marketing purposes.

 _Use of Non-Personal Information_

We may combine Personal and Non-Personal Information about you, and may combine this information with information from external sources. Third parties may also use Non-Personal Information in order to display advertising that reflects the interests and preferences of our users.

We also use Cookies in order to conduct surveys for our own use and on behalf of our advertisers. These Cookies are used to determine whether you have seen certain content or advertising so that we may request your opinions. We may also use Cookies to authenticate respondents or to help you pick up where you left off in a survey. If you have Cookies disabled you may not be able to participate in some surveys.

 _Remarketing on Third Party Web Sites_

The FSND web site employs Google AdWords Remarketing ("Adwords") to advertise FSND goods and services across the Internet. This is how it works: AdWords uses Cookies to track which parts of the FSND web site you have viewed. Then, using the Non-Personal Information obtained through those Cookies, third party vendors (e.g., Google) display FSND ads specifically tailored to you on third party web sites that you visit. This way, we are able to advertise FSND goods and services in a way that best suits your specific needs.

If you do not wish to participate in AdWords, you can opt out by visiting Google's Ads Preferences Manager. You can also opt out of any third-party vendor's use of Cookies by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices.

 _Research and Measurement Activities_

Information that FSND collects about you may be combined by FSND with other information available to FSND through third parties for research and measurement purposes, including measuring the effectiveness of content, advertising or programs. This information from other sources may include age, gender, demographic, location, personal interests, product purchase activity or other information. We may report aggregate information, which is not able to be identified back to an individual user of the FSND web site, to our current or prospective advertisers and other business partners. We do not sell or share any Personal Information with any third parties, except contractors performing services on our behalf who agree not to use this information received from us for any purpose other than performing services on our behalf.

 _Disclosures to FSND Operations and Maintenance Contractor_

FSND contractors sometimes have limited access to your Personal and Non-Personal Information in the course of providing products or services to FSND. These contractors include vendors and suppliers that provide us with technology, services, data analysis, research, advertising and marketing assistance and/or content for the operation and maintenance of the FSND web site. We contractually require that our operations and maintenance contractors: (1) protect the privacy of your Personal and Non-Personal Information consistent with this Privacy Policy and (2) not use or disclose your Personal or Non-Personal Information for any purpose other than providing the limited service or function for FSND.

 _Disclosures to Third Party Web Sites_

Certain content, services and advertisements offered to you through the FSND web site are served on, or contain links to, web sites hosted and operated by a company other than FSND ("Third Party Web Sites"). FSND does not disclose your Personal Information to these Third Party Web Sites without your consent, but you should be aware that any information you disclose to the other web sites once you access these other web sites is not subject to this Privacy Policy. FSND does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices of these Third Party Web Sites. You should review the privacy policy posted on the other web site to understand how that Third Party Web Site collects and uses your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

 _Third Party Promotions_

From time to time, FSND may provide you with the opportunity to opt-in to receive promotional offers and marketing communications from our affiliates and commercial partners. If you do not opt-in, FSND will not send you any such promotional offers. You may also opt-out of receiving any such promotional offers at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in the body of the communication.

 _Mandatory Disclosures_

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or as specifically agreed to by you, FSND will not disclose any Personal Information it gathers from you through the FSND web site. We may only release Personal Information to third parties:

  1. To comply with legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order.
  2. In special cases, such as to protect property or defend or assert legal rights.
  3. In the event of a corporate change in control resulting from, for example, a sale to another entity, or in the event of a sale of assets or a bankruptcy, FSND reserves the right to transfer your Personal Information to the new party in control or the party acquiring assets. In the event of such a change, your Personal Information will continue to be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy unless any changes to the Privacy Policy are made in accordance with the section below titled "Changes to This Privacy Policy."

 **How We Protect Your Information**

 _Internal Safeguards_

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We use commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard Personal Information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.

Despite FSND's efforts to protect your Personal Information, there is always some risk that an unauthorized third party may find a way around our security systems or that transmissions of your information over the Internet may be intercepted.

We will retain your Personal Information as long as your account is active or needed to provide you services. At any time you can remove your Personal Information or instruct us to remove it, but you should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to FSND from our servers. FSND tools that collect and store Personal Information allow you to correct, update or review information you have submitted by going back to the specific tool, logging-in and making the desired changes. We will also retain your Personal Information as necessary to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

 **Children Under the Age of 13**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. The FSND web site is not designed or intended to attract children under the age of 13. The FSND web site does not collect Personal Information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13.

 **Choices You Have Regarding Your Personal Information**

There are several options available to you if you do not want your Personal Information used by FSND as provided in this Privacy Policy.

 _Reviewing and Modifying Your Personal Information_

At any time, you may update Personal Information that is stored on the FSND web site or change your account preferences on the FSND web site:

  1. You may unsubscribe to any of our email updates, posts, newsletters or products by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any message
  2. You may contact us at kari@rebootwithjoe.com

 _Disabling Cookies_

Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject Cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar. If you reject our Cookies, certain of the functions and conveniences of the FSND web site may not work properly but you do not have to accept our Cookies in order to productively use the FSND web site. It is important to note that in order to use the opt-out services described below, you must not reject all Cookies because these opt-out procedures work by placing Cookies on your browser that enable these opt-out procedures to function. The "opt-out Cookies" are placed, for example, in order to help prevent the placement of Cookies used for the targeting of advertising.

Certain Ad Servers allow you to prevent them from collecting data through the use of Cookies. In order to do so, you must Opt-out of such data collection with each individual site. You can find additional information and resources about how to opt out of advertising and related Cookies by visiting the World Privacy Forum's site at www.worldprivacyforum.org.

In addition, as set forth above, you can opt out of any third-party vendor's use of Cookies by visiting www.networkadvertising.org/choices.

 _Electronic Communications You Send to FSND_

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information, content, business information, ideas, concepts or inventions that you send to FSND by email, text message or other means of electronic communication. If you want to keep content or business information, ideas, concepts or inventions private or proprietary, do not send them electronically to FSND.

 **California Privacy Rights**

California Law permits those visitors to our web site who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at our address set forth above and include your name and the address to which you would like us to respond.

 **Cross-Border Transfer**

Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where FSND has facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using our products and services you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules than in your country.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at kari@rebootwithjoe.com. You can also contact FSND's Privacy Office at:

99 University Place, 3rd Floor  
New York, NY 10003  
Attn: Kari Thorstensen

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, so it is suggested that you check the FSND web site from time to time to ensure that you know about our current policy. We reserve the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy or any of our tools or services at any time and any changes will be effective upon being posted unless we advise otherwise. If we make any material changes to this policy we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified when you register) and/or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this website for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, we ask that you do not register with us and that you do not use the FSND web site. Please exit the FSND web site immediately if you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Effective October 2, 2013
